<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>Hacking Diaries</title>
    
    
    <description>This website is a virtual proof that I&apos;m awesome</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting root user access so easily? How come!</title>
        <description>
          How to take advantage of system binaries to get root access on a host - 
          Oh! Hi! Didn’t see you there little fellow. You may wonder how you can get root access as quick as the blink of an eye… So you are in the right place. What do I mean by root access? You may be familiar with the Windows’ Administrator account, that, like...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-07-14-rooting-is-easy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-07-14-rooting-is-easy/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rooting with forgotten CronJobs</title>
        <description>
          How to take advantage of forgotten cronjobs to get root access on a host - 
          As you might have guessed by the title, in this article, we will explore another scenario where we could take advantage of forgotten cronjobs to gain our precious root access. BUT FIRST, if you are new here, or missed the previous articles about this, don’t hesitate to pay a visit...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-07-14-rooting-forgotten-cronjobs/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-07-14-rooting-forgotten-cronjobs/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rooting with Docker Containers</title>
        <description>
          How to take advantage of container creation to get root access on a host - 
          Will you believe me if I tell you that Docker is a hacker? Let me show you how to take advantage of Docker containers so you can access any high privilege file or perform any command as root. To begin with, if you already know Docker, you might be aware...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-02-23-rooting-with-docker/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-02-23-rooting-with-docker/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sample blog post</title>
        <description>
          Each post also has a subtitle - 
          This is a demo post to show you how to write blog posts with markdown. I strongly encourage you to take 5 minutes to learn how to write in markdown - it’ll teach you how to transform regular text into bold/italics/headings/tables/etc. Here is some bold text Here is a secondary...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-28-test-markdown/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-02-28-test-markdown/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flake it till you make it</title>
        <description>
          Excerpt from Soulshaping by Jeff Brown - 
          Under what circumstances should we step off a path? When is it essential that we finish what we start? If I bought a bag of peanuts and had an allergic reaction, no one would fault me if I threw it out. If I ended a relationship with a woman who...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
