<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>Hacking Diaries</title>
    
    
    <description>This website is a virtual proof that I&apos;m awesome</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>I&apos;ve read OWASP Web App Pentesting Guide so you don&apos;t have to... Part I.</title>
        <description>
          Web App Pentesting: Information Gathering - 
          Here I am, as the hero internet needs, to give you all an easy to digest action list of the thick OWASP WebApp Penetration Testing Guide v4. The Penetration Testing Methodology is made of 12 different steps an ethical hacker must take when performing a penetration test, and we will...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-01-26-owasp-information-gathering/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-01-26-owasp-information-gathering/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Ways NOT to store secrets in Docker Containers</title>
        <description>
          Can your secrets be compromised in a containerized deployment? Are they safe enough from no desired snoopers? - 
          What do I mean by “secrets”? Passwords, API Tokens, Certificates… You name it. Whatever information your code needs to access what it needs to access - lovely redundancy :) -. Your webserver maybe needs a database password so that it can access a table to do whatever it needs to...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-08-09-not-store-secrets-docker/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-08-09-not-store-secrets-docker/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rooting with forgotten CronJobs</title>
        <description>
          How to take advantage of forgotten cronjobs to get root access on a host - 
          As you might have guessed by the title, in this article, we will explore another scenario where we could take advantage of forgotten cronjobs to gain our precious root access. BUT FIRST, if you are new here, or missed the previous articles about this, don’t hesitate to pay a visit...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-07-21-rooting-forgotten-cronjobs/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-07-21-rooting-forgotten-cronjobs/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting root user access so easily? How come!</title>
        <description>
          How to take advantage of system binaries to get root access on a host - 
          Oh! Hi! Didn’t see you there little fellow. You may wonder how you can get root access as quick as the blink of an eye… So you are in the right place. What do I mean by root access? You may be familiar with the Windows’ Administrator account, that, like...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-07-14-rooting-is-easy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-07-14-rooting-is-easy/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rooting with Docker Containers</title>
        <description>
          How to take advantage of container creation to get root access on a host - 
          Will you believe me if I tell you that Docker is a hacker? Let me show you how to take advantage of Docker containers so you can access any high privilege file or perform any command as root. To begin with, if you already know Docker, you might be aware...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-02-23-rooting-with-docker/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-02-23-rooting-with-docker/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
